RG 071, Department of Housing
Connecticut State Library
- Series 6. Policy and Planning Division, 1984; 1 cubic foot
  - Correspondence and face sheets, 1984; 1992-022; 1 cubic foot (Box 1)
- Series 7. Management Analysts, undated; 1 cubic foot
  - Policy and Procedures Manual, undated; 1990-006; 1 cubic foot (Box 1)
    Policy and procedure manuals for Administration, Management, and Development Divisions.